Guide to the New York University Collection of Papyri, Ostraka, and Cuneiform Tablets MSS.559
Fales Library and Special Collections
New York University Collection of Papyri, Ostraka, and Cuneiform Tablets
circa 1st Century-7th Century CE
Fales Library and Special Collections
New York University
MSS.559
58.5 linear feet in 44 small flat boxes, 12 oversize flat boxes, and 1 custom box
This collection consists of ancient inscriptions and writing artifacts, including papyri, clay tablets, and ostraka. The collection contains over 2,000 papyri fragments, 86 ostraka, and two cuneiform tablets, primarily dating from the 1st-7th centuries CE. The papyri, the majority of which is in Greek, is primarily documentary in nature, and includes evidence of daily life through accounts, deeds, wills, loans, receipts, petitions, and letters. The collection also includes ostraka, cuneiform tablets, and mummy fragments as artifacts of early writing.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Other Finding Aids
Item level information on the papyri in this collection, including date estimates, language information, and photographic documentation, is available through the Advanced Papyrological Information System (APIS) database at Papyri.info.
Custodial History
New York University's collection of papyri and other early writing artifacts was acquired in two installments. In 1924, about 500 items were identified by English papyrologist H.I. Bell at the excavation site of the ancient Egyptian village of Karanis. The second installment was acquired in 1932 by Professor Casper J. Kraemer, Jr., Chairman of the Department of Classics, historically referred to as the "Cairo Purchase." There is little documentation on the materials that comprise this accretion to the collection. More recently, additional items have been added to the collection through faculty in the NYU Department of Classics, including Professor Bluma L. Trell and Professor Lionel Casson. The materials in this collection were acquired in a historical context of western archaeological extraction of African and Mediterranean cultural heritage.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of ancient inscriptions and writing artifacts, including papyri, clay tablets, and ostraka. The collection contains over 2,000 papyri fragments, 86 ostraka, and two cuneiform tablets, primarily dating from the 1st-7th centuries CE. The papyri, the majority of which is in Greek, is primarily documentary in nature, and includes evidence of daily life through accounts, deeds, wills, loans, receipts, petitions, and letters. The collection also includes ostraka, cuneiform tablets, and mummy fragments as artifacts of early writing.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into four series based on format:
Series I. Papyri
Series II. Ostraka
Series III. Cuneiform Tablets
Series IV. Mummy Wrappings
Documentary papyri; Manuscripts (Papyri); Ostraka; Cuneiform; Inscriptions, Greek; Inscriptions, Egyptian; Sumerian language; Written communication; History, Ancient; Writing -- History
- Series I. Papyri Fragments, 55 Linear Feet in 44 small flat boxes and 2 oversize flat boxes
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0001, 1 fragment 22.5 x 29 cm (Box 44, Item P.NYU inv 0001)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0002, 1 fragment 26 x 37 cm (Box 44, Item P.NYU inv 0002)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0003, 1 fragment 27.5 x 13 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0003)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0004, 1 fragment 22 x 19.5 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0004)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0005, 1 fragment 35 x 13 cm (Box 44, Item P.NYU inv 0005)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0006, 1 fragment 16.5 x 19 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0006)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0007.01, 1 fragment 08 x 11 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0007.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0007.02, 1 fragment 11.5 x 8 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0007.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0008, 1 fragment 16 x 14.5 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0008)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0009, 1 fragment 15.5 x 22 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0009)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0010, 1 fragment 26.5 x 9.5 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0010)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0012, 1 fragment 06 x 9 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0012)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0013.01, 1 fragment 12 x 21 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0013.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0013.02, 1 fragment 11.0 x 12.5 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0013.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0014.01, 3 fragment 14.0 x 11.0 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0014.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0014.02, 3 fragment 04 x 11 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0014.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0014.03, 3 fragment 04.5 x 5 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0014.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0015, 1 fragment 24 x 18 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0015)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0016, 1 fragment 06 x 11.5 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0016)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0017, 1 fragment 10.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0017)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0018, 1 fragment 12 x 11.5 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0018)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0019, 1 fragment 06.5 x 20 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0019)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0020, 1 fragment 22.5 x 12.5 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0020)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0021, 1 fragment 25 x 4 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0021)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0022, 1 fragment 17 x 13 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0022)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0023.01, 23 fragments 08.5 x 4.5 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0023.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0023.02, 23 fragments 08.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0023.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0023.03, 23 fragments 08 x 4 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0023.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0023.04, 23 fragments 05 x 4 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0023.04)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0023.05, 23 fragments 03 x 02 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0023.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0023.06, 23 fragments 05 x 2 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0023.06)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0023.07, 23 fragments 02 x1.5 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0023.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0023.08, 23 fragments 02.5 x 2 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0023.08)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0023.09, 23 fragments 02 x 2 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0023.09)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0023.10, 23 fragments 03 x 2 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0023.10)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0023.11, 23 fragments 04 x 2.5 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0023.11)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0023.12, 23 fragments 04 x 3.5 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0023.12)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0023.13, 23 fragments 04 x 4.5 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0023.13)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0023.14, 23 fragments 05 x 1.5 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0023.14)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0023.15, 23 fragments 08.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0023.15)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0023.16, 23 fragments 02.5 x 0.5 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0023.16)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0023.17, 23 fragments 02.5 x 1 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0023.17)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0023.18, 23 fragments 02 x 2 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0023.18)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0023.19, 23 fragments 02.5 x 1 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0023.19)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0023.20, 23 fragments 01.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0023.20)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0023.21, 23 fragments 00.5 x 1 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0023.21)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0023.22, 23 fragments 02 x 0.5 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0023.22)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0024, 1 fragment 17 x 14.5 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0024)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0025, 1 fragment 11 x 16 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0025)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0026, 1 fragment 10 x 20.5 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0026)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0027, 1 fragment 23.5 x 8 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0027)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0029, 1 fragment 09 x 21 cm (Box 41, Item P.NYU inv 0029)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0030, 1 fragment 23 x 11 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0030)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0031, 1 fragment 23.5 x 10 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0031)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0032, 1 fragment 16.5 x 16 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0032)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0033, 1 fragment 15 x 9.5 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0033)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0034, 1 fragment 13 x 6 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0034)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0035, 1 fragment 08 x 15.5 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0035)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0036a, 1 fragment 18.5 x 21 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0036a)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0036b, 1 fragment 14.5 x 14 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0036b)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0036c, 1 fragment 12.5 x 09.5 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0036c)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0036d, 1 fragment 19 x 15.5 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0036d)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0037, 1 fragment 25 x 18 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0037)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0038, 1 fragment 34.5 x 10.5 cm (Box 44, Item P.NYU inv 0038)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0039, 1 fragment 04.5 x 5 cm (Box 41, Item P.NYU inv 0039)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0040, 1 fragment 14.5 x 23 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0040)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0041, 1 fragment 07.5 x 6 cm (Box 41, Item P.NYU inv 0041)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0042, 1 fragment 23 x 43 cm (Box 44, Item P.NYU inv 0042)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0043, 1 fragment 24 x 38 cm (Box 44, Item P.NYU inv 0043)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0044, 1 fragment 25 x 17 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0044)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0045, 1 fragment 25 x 12.5 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0045)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0046, 1 fragment 26 x 36 cm (Box 44, Item P.NYU inv 0046)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0047, 1 fragment 26 x 31 cm (Box 44, Item P.NYU inv 0047)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0048, 1 fragment 28 x 22 cm (Box 44, Item P.NYU inv 0048)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0049, 1 fragment 28 x 12 cm (Box 44, Item P.NYU inv 0049)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0050, 1 fragment 18.0 x 71.5 cm (Box 45, Item P.NYU inv 0050)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0051, 1 fragment 28.8 x 18 cm (Box 44, Item P.NYU inv 0051)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0052.01, 3 fragments 28.5 x 18 cm (Box 44, Item P.NYU inv 0052.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0052.02, 3 fragments 02.5 x 1 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0052.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0052.03, 3 fragments 08.5 x 2 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0052.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0053, 1 fragment 29 x 8.5 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0053)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0054, 1 fragment 03.5 x 4.5 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0054)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0055, 1 fragment 24.5 x 11 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0055)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0056.01, 7 fragments 10.0 x 12.0 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0056.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0056.02, 7 fragments 08 x 3.5 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0056.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0056.03, 7 fragments 02 x 2 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0056.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0056.04, 7 fragments 02.5 x 1 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0056.04)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0056.05, 7 fragments 21 x 6.5 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0056.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0056.06, 7 fragments 01 x 2 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0056.06)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0056.07, 7 fragments 15 x 7 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0056.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0057.01, 1 fragment 14.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0057.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0057.02, 1 fragment 05.5 x 4.5 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0057.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0057.03, 1 fragment 23.5 x 7 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0057.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0058, 1 fragment 24.5 x 8 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0058)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0059, 1 fragment 27 x 8.5 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0059)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0060, 1 fragment 26 x 18 cm (Box 38, Item P.NYU inv 0060)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0061, 1 fragment 27 x 13 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0061)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0063, 1 fragment 24 x 8 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0063)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0064, 1 fragment 18 x 35 cm (Box 44, Item P.NYU inv 0064)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0065, 1 fragment 21.0 x 11.0 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0065)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0066, 1 fragment 21 x 17 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0066)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0067.01, 2 fragments 24.5 x 34.5 cm (Box 44, Item P.NYU inv 0067.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0067.02, 2 fragments 03 x 2 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0067.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0068, 1 fragment 10 x 13 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0068)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0069, 1 fragment 18 x 9 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0069)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0070, 1 fragment 04 x 6 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0070)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0071, 1 fragment 08.5 x 09.0 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0071)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0072, 1 fragment 13.5 x 11 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0072)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0073, 1 fragment 16.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0073)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0074.01, 1 fragment 18 x 17.5 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0074.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0074.02, 1 fragment 06 x 5.5 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0074.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0074.03, 1 fragment 01.5 x 1 cm (Box 1, Item P.NYU inv 0074.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0075, 1 fragment 26 x 7 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0075)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0076, 1 fragment 17.5 x 13 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0076)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0077, 1 fragment 18.5 x 8 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0077)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0078, 1 fragment 30 x 14.5 cm (Box 44, Item P.NYU inv 0078)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0079, 1 fragment 08 x13 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0079)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0080, 1 fragment 22.5 x 10 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0080)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0081, 1 fragment 29 x 12 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0081)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0082, 1 fragment 24.5 x 14.5 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0082)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0083, 1 fragment 18.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0083)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0084, 1 fragment 09.5 x 4.5 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0084)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0085, 1 fragment 10.5 x 7 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0085)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0086, 1 fragment 10.5 x 5 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0086)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0087, 1 fragment 12.0 x 18.0 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0087)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0088, 1 fragment 13.0 x 20.0 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0088)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0089, 1 fragment 07.5 x 17.5 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0089)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0090, 1 fragment 06.5 x 7.6 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0090)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0091, 1 fragment 30.5 x 27 cm (Box 44, Item P.NYU inv 0091)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0092, 1 fragment 07.5 x 15.0 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0092)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0093, 1 fragment 09 x 06 cm (Box 41, Item P.NYU inv 0093)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0094, 1 fragment 16 x 8.5 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0094)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0095, 1 fragment 08.5 x 11.0 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0095)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0096.01, 1 fragment 26 x 18.5 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0096.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0096.02, 1 fragment 0.05 x 1.5 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0096.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0097, 1 fragment 20 x 22 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0097)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0098.01, 1 fragment 14 x 10 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0098.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0098.02, 1 fragment 00.5 x 3 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0098.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0099, 1 fragment 15 x 13 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0099)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0100, 1 fragment 12.5 x 17.0 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0100)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0101, 1 fragment 14.5 x 16.5 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0101)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0102, 1 fragment 06 x 8 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0102)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0103.01, 1 fragment 12 x 4 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0103.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0103.02, 1 fragment 01 x 3.5 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0103.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0104, 1 fragment 11.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0104)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0105, 1 fragment 08.0 x 14.0 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0105)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0106, 1 fragment 10.5 x 4 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0106)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0107, 1 fragment 17.5 x 13.0 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0107)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0108, 1 fragment 16.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0108)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0109, 1 fragment 27.5 x 11 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0109)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0110.01, 3 fragments 17 x 7 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0110.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0110.02, 3 fragments 07 x 5 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0110.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0110.03, 3 fragments 15.5 x 5.5 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0110.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0111, 1 fragment 17 x 15 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0111)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0112, 1 fragment 08.5 x 11.5 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0112)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0113, 1 fragment 07 x 9 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0113)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0114, 1 fragment 17 x 7 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0114)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0115, 1 fragment 02 x 2.5 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0115)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0116.01, 1 fragment 16 x 36 cm (Box 44, Item P.NYU inv 0116.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0116.02, 1 fragment 03 x 5.5 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0116.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0116.03, 1 fragment 03 x 2.5 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0116.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0117, 1 fragment 10 x 8 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0117)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0118, 1 fragment 18.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0118)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0119, 1 fragment 16 x 11 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0119)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0120, 1 fragment 04 x 12.5 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0120)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0121, 1 fragment 07 x 2 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0121)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0122, 1 fragment 09.5 x 10 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0122)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0123, 1 fragment 10 x 10.5 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0123)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0124, 1 fragment 11 x 13 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0124)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0125, 1 fragment 10 x 7 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0125)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0126, 1 fragment 09.5 x 08.5 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0126)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0127.01, 1 fragment 01 x 4.5 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0127.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0127.02, 1 fragment 02 x 4 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0127.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0127.03, 1 fragment 01.5 x 4.5 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0127.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0127.04, 1 fragment 03.5 x 4.5 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0127.04)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0128, 1 fragment 07.5 x 03 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0128)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0129, 1 fragment 14.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0129)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0130, 1 fragment 12.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0130)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0131, 1 fragment 05.5 x 3.5 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0131)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0132.01, 1 fragment 04.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0132.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0132.02, 1 fragment 10.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0132.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0132.03, 1 fragment 05 x 3 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0132.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0133, 1 fragment 08.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0133)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0134, 1 fragment 03 x 8.5 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0134)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0135, 1 fragment 03 x 3 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0135)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0136, 1 fragment 05.5 x 3 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0136)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0137, 1 fragment 04 x 4 cm (Box 2, Item P.NYU inv 0137)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0138, 1 fragment 04 x 5 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0138)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0139.01, 1 fragment 03.5 x 2 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0139.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0139.02, 1 fragment 04.5 x 3 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0139.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0140, 1 fragment 01 x 10.5 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0140)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0141, 1 fragment 02.5 x 4 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0141)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0142, 1 fragment 01.5 x 3 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0142)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0143, 1 fragment 03 x 2 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0143)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0144, 1 fragment 02.5 x 3 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0144)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0145, 1 fragment 01.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0145)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0146, 1 fragment 03 x 02 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0146)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0147, 1 fragment 03 x 02 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0147)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0148, 1 fragment 02 x 1.5 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0148)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0149, 1 fragment 01.5 x3 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0149)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0150, 1 fragment 17.5 x 3.5 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0150)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0151, 1 fragment 09 x 12.5 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0151)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0152, 1 fragment 13.5 x 11.5 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0152)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0153, 1 fragment 05.5 x 5 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0153)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0154, 1 fragment 21 x 7.5 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0154)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0155.01, 1 fragment 08 x 3.5 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0155.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0155.02, 1 fragment 13.5 x 9 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0155.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0156, 1 fragment 05.5 x 14 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0156)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0157, 1 fragment 06 x 3.5 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0157)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0158, 1 fragment 06 x 8 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0158)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0159, 1 fragment 08.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0159)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0160, 1 fragment 09 x 7 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0160)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0161, 1 fragment 07.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0161)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0162, 1 fragment 03 x 07 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0162)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0163, 1 fragment 05 x 4 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0163)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0164, 1 fragment 05 x 3 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0164)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0165, 1 fragment 03.5 x 5 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0165)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0166, 1 fragment 04.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0166)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0167, 1 fragment 02.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0167)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0168, 1 fragment 08 x 5.5 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0168)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0169, 1 fragment 07.5 x 2 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0169)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0170.01, 1 fragment 03.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0170.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0170.02, 1 fragment 04 x 3 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0170.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0171, 1 fragment 02.5 x 2 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0171)